{
    "id": "db3a249d4a21450eac4767f2f01e9236",
    "title": "Simple Future Tense Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "In two days, I ………………….. my results.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will know",
                "would know",
                "will be knowing"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "9e3fda43c5014feaa1aef12b2808f555"
        },
        {
            "question": "‘There is the doorbell.’ ‘I ………………..’",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "would go",
                "am going",
                "will go"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "69bb9cea919d4331b83f46def7ca212d"
        },
        {
            "question": "You ..................... this decision.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will be regretting",
                "will regret",
                "would regret"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "8973c963681b4fcba1f24907f821d8c1"
        },
        {
            "question": "We ………………….. what happened to her.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "would never know",
                "will never know",
                "will never be knowing"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6babae2f3e7242a19d4431a8fb33b0a9"
        },
        {
            "question": "The whole nation ……………….. proud of you.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "will be",
                "would be"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "872e8a8b882c4405a3537fb0053192a0"
        },
        {
            "question": "That …………………. our gift to the school.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will be",
                "would be",
                "will have been"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "1a9a18a2d66e49b5893797664285755b"
        },
        {
            "question": "Kind words ………………….. others joy.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will give",
                "would give",
                "will be giving"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "6e233d38d25e40c2b19af77c0cab5da7"
        },
        {
            "question": "This piece of wisdom ………………. you ten dollars.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will cost",
                "would cost",
                "will be costing"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "50e146e7e96346da82c08a002ddadbdc"
        },
        {
            "question": "You ..................... my position.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will never understand",
                "would never understand",
                "never understand"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "1d80ea49b3dc47faa1014327e75ae256"
        },
        {
            "question": "Someday I ........................ a novel.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will be writing",
                "will write",
                "would write"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "1327c8aab6fe4d9786638a4db2cfe30c"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ...................... this.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will not permit",
                "would not permit",
                "will not be permitting"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "71e5c19d95a34704aa00291a680e0388"
        },
        {
            "question": "He .....................… the test.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "cannot pass",
                "will not pass",
                "will not be passing"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f6539923c5e84748b746545f1b3ee1d6"
        }
    ]
}